<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MedFC</string>
    <string name="account_type">com.example.reico_000.prescriptionreadernfc.account</string>
    <string name="provider_authority">com.example.reico_000.prescriptionreadernfc.provider</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>

    <string name="title_section1">Scan Medications</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Medication List</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Prescription Date List</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Reported Symptoms List</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_legends">Legends</string>
    <string name="action_report">Report Symptoms</string>

    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_scanItem1">Scan Item 1</string>
    <string name="action_scanItem2">Scan Item 2</string>
    <string name="action_scanItem3">Scan Item 3</string>
    <string name="action_showNotification">Show Notification</string>
    <string name="action_eraseTagData">Erase Tag Data</string>
    <string name="action_loadStubConsumption">Load Stub Consumption</string>
    <string name="action_termsAndConds">Terms And Conditions</string>
    <string name="action_getConsumption1">Get Consumption 1</string>
    <string name="action_getConsumption2">Get Consumption 2</string>
    <string name="action_changeReminderTiming">Change Reminder Timing</string>
    <string name="action_stopTakingMedicine">Stop Taking Medication</string>
    <string name="action_showMoreInfo">Show More Info</string>
    <string name="action_scanMedication">Scan Medication</string>
    <string name="action_viewOrEditRemarks">View/Edit Remarks</string>

    <!-- LOGIN and REGISTER -->
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Name</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Sign up now.</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registred! Login Me.</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="btn_logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="name">Fullname</string>

    <string name="termsAndConds">&lt;b>General Information&lt;/b>
&lt;br>The MedFC app project is a research collaboration between the Departments of Pharmacy and
Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering, National University of Singapore. Please visit the
‘About Us’ section on the &lt;a href="https://www.onco-informatics.com/medfc/index.php">
MedFC website&lt;/a> for details of the research team.

&lt;br>&lt;br>By using this product, you acknowledge the acceptance of the following terms
and conditions, including the restrictions, disclaimers and limitations. You agree
that we are not responsible for the results of your decisions resulting from the
use of the product. This includes, but is not limited to, your choice of whether to
seek or not to seek professional medical care, specific medical treatments and/or
drug therapy.

&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;b>About MedFC app&lt;/b>
&lt;br>MedFC is a smartphone app intended for patients with chronic medical
conditions and/or their caregivers. The purpose of the app is to help patients
manage their medications easily through monitoring of their medication
adherence patterns and clinical outcomes. The app provides a variety of
functionalities including medication reminders, source of medication
information, recording of symptoms related to medication side effects or disease
condition, and a means for tracking medication taking patterns. This app also
allows healthcare providers to monitor their patients’ medication adherence
patterns through a clinician interface.

&lt;br>&lt;br>The MedFC app is intended to complement patients’ current methods of
monitoring medication adherence. Patients should not and must not solely rely
on the app for taking their medications on time. In cases where any hardware or
software on the user’s device prevents the app from operating as intended or is
broken, or if the power is turned off, or if the app is not enabled, MedFC may not
function as intended. As a patient user, you acknowledge that MedFC’s reminder
system depends on the preferences that you make in the settings of the app
and/or your smartphone, and information that you enter, if you choose to change
the details of your medication schedule that is programed by your health
professional.

&lt;br>&lt;br>The contents of the MedFC app are not intended to be a substitute for
professional medical advice, diagnosis or treatment. Patients should always seek
the advice of their physician, pharmacist or other qualified health provider with
any questions they may have regarding their medications or medical condition.
Every effort has been made to ensure that the app contains accurate and up-to-
date medication information, but no guarantee is made to that effect. We are not
responsible for any misinterpretation of medication information by the user.
Additionally, the medication information contained herein may also be time
sensitive. Reliance on any information accessed through the MedFC app is solely
at the user’s own risk.

&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;b>About the MedFC application&lt;/b>
&lt;br>The MedFC application has three components: (1) clinician interface, (2)
patient interface, (3) caregiver interface.

&lt;br>&lt;br>The clinician interface is intended for clinicians who are involved in the supply of
medicines and provision of pharmaceutical care to patients. The interface
enables the clinician to enter patient details including their names, the name and
dosages of their medications and other medication-related information.
This information will be utilized to encode a Near Field Communication (NFC)
sticker that will be part of the labelling on the patient’s medication package. The
clinician can also monitor the patient’s medication adherence patterns and
reported symptoms. Information required during signup for access to this application includes,
the user’s full name, NRIC/FIN, email address, and login password. The collected information is
stored for as long as the user has access to the interface and can only be accessed
by the MedFC Team, for the purpose of analysing user statistics. No information
will be revealed to any third party for advertising or other purposes except those
cases where we are obliged to reveal the information by a court order.

&lt;br>&lt;br>The patient web interface is designed as a convenient way for patients to
monitor their medication adherence levels. The caregiver interface enables
caregivers to track the medication adherence patterns of the patient they care
for. The patient has to endorse the caregiver before access is granted,
unless in exceptional cases.

&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;b>Privacy Policy&lt;/b>
&lt;br>Any personally identifiable information collected from the usage of the app
remains highly confidential and will not be used for any other purpose besides
facilitating the usage of the app. The app will access patient’s personal
information entered in the clinician’s web interface. Personal information
collected includes the user’s full name, and NRIC number. The details of the
medications that the patient takes are also accessed. The app also collects
symptom information that patients enter. The collected information is stored in
the MedFC database for as long as the user has access to the app and can only be
accessed by his/her healthcare professional, and the MedFC Team for the
purpose of analysing user statistics. No information will be revealed to any third
party for advertising or other purposes except those cases where we are obliged
to reveal the information by a court order.

&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;b>Advertising&lt;/b>
&lt;br>The MedFC app is a non-commercial app developed by a collaboration between
the Departments of Pharmacy and Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering, National
University of Singapore. The app is not sponsored by any other organisation and
is not funded by advertising. The MedFC team does not have any direct conflict of
interest with any commercial organiszation or organiszations that may bias the
information provided by the app.

&lt;br>&lt;br>The MedFC website does not intentionally use cookies. Cookies can be disabled
from the settings menu of your Internet browser. (&lt;a href="http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies">
Internet Explorer&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&amp;redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies">
Firefox&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677">Safari&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&amp;answer=95647">
Google Chrome&lt;/a>)

&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;b>User Risks&lt;/b>
&lt;br>The absence of a warning for a given medication or combination of medications
does not indicate that the medication or medication combination is safe, effective
or appropriate for any given patient and should not be interpreted as such.
By using the MedFC app and clinician interface, the user acknowledges that
he/she has been made aware of the disclaimers in this agreement, including
those which state that the app is not a substitute for professional advice, and that
the MedFC team and their institutions make no warranty on the accuracy,
validity, completeness or availability of the information cited in this app.

&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;b>Contact us:&lt;/b>
&lt;br>Please visit the ‘Contact Us’ section on the &lt;a href="https://www.onco-informatics.com/medfc/index.php#contactus">
MedFC website&lt;/a>.</string>

    <string name="legends_text">&lt;b>Per Dosage&lt;/b>&lt;br>Amount of medicine that you need to take every time
&lt;br>&lt;b>Balance&lt;/b>&lt;br>The amount of medicine that you have left
&lt;br>&lt;b>Consumption Time&lt;/b>&lt;br>The time when you are required to take your medication </string>
<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="patient_name">Patient Name:</string>
    <string name="brand_name">Brand Name:</string>
    <string name="generic_name">Generic Name:</string>
    <string name="dosage_form">Dosage Form:</string>
    <string name="per_dosage">Per Dosage:</string>
    <string name="total_dosage">Balance:</string>
    <string name="consumption_time">Consumption Time:</string>
    <string name="frequency">Frequency:</string>
    <string name="prescription_date">Prescription Date:</string>
    <string name="consume">Consume\nMedications</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset\nFields</string>
    <string name="save">Save&lt;br>Medication</string>
</resources>
